
--- MATCH 1 ---
RAW BEFORE TEXT:
'o their story." We have two wonderful family birthdays to celebrate this month. On January 10, we celebrate Laura Kelsy.'
LAST WORDS BEFORE <cend>:
['celebrate', 'Laura', 'Kelsy.']
ANCHOR STORED:
celebrate Laura Kelsy.
REMOVING MARKER: <cend>

--- MATCH 2 ---
RAW BEFORE TEXT:
' Just a couple of days later, birthday cheers go to Newton Kiprono on January 12.'
LAST WORDS BEFORE <cend>:
['on', 'January', '12.']
ANCHOR STORED:
on January 12.
REMOVING MARKER: <cend>

--- MATCH 3 ---
RAW BEFORE TEXT:
'al occasion for lasting love, partnership, and commitment. On January 24, we remember and celebrate the union of Pomner.'
LAST WORDS BEFORE <cend>:
['union', 'of', 'Pomner.']
ANCHOR STORED:
union of Pomner.
REMOVING MARKER: <cend>

=== FINAL OUTPUT ===

CLEAN TEXT (for TTS):

What a wonderful start to the New Year! WeÆre kicking off January with some beautiful celebrations, and we are so excited to honor the special people who make our family shine.

"Let's turn our attention first to those who are adding another wonderful year to their story." We have two wonderful family birthdays to celebrate this month. On January 10, we celebrate Laura Kelsy. Just a couple of days later, birthday cheers go to Newton Kiprono on January 12. We wish both of you the very happiest of birthdays and hope your year is filled with joy.

And finally, January also marks a special occasion for lasting love, partnership, and commitment. On January 24, we remember and celebrate the union of Pomner. May this year bring continued happiness and many more wonderful memories together!

STORED ANCHORS (for timestamp matching):
1. celebrate Laura Kelsy.
2. on January 12.
3. union of Pomner.
('What a wonderful start to the New Year! WeÆre kicking off January with some beautiful celebrations, and we are so excited to honor the special people who make our family shine.\n\n"Let\'s turn our attention first to those who are adding another wonderful year to their story." We have two wonderful family birthdays to celebrate this month. On January 10, we celebrate Laura Kelsy. Just a couple of days later, birthday cheers go to Newton Kiprono on January 12. We wish both of you the very happiest of birthdays and hope your year is filled with joy.\n\nAnd finally, January also marks a special occasion for lasting love, partnership, and commitment. On January 24, we remember and celebrate the union of Pomner. May this year bring continued happiness and many more wonderful memories together!', ['celebrate Laura Kelsy.', 'on January 12.', 'union of Pomner.'])
